(Sheldon:)I wanted to apologize
for my behavior today. It...
(Sheldon:)It was unnecessary.
(Sheldon:)This is warm.
(Sheldon:)Oh, and also, I am willing to
forego the bathroom schedule.
(Amy:)Oh. Really?
Why does she get that?!
We never got that!
(Penny:)Do you want him back?
(Leonard:)I'm very happy for you.
(Sheldon:)Amy, you should know
(Sheldon:)I was never really interested
in seeing other women.
(Sheldon:)And to prove how
serious I am about us,
(Sheldon:)I'm willing to take our
relationship to the next level.
(Sheldon:)Amy Farrah Fowler,
(Sheldon:)will you share
this toothbrush holder with me?
(Amy:)I would love to.
(Leonard:)Did we really
(Leonard:)need to be
here for this?
(Penny:)Call me crazy,
but I found it moving.